designobserver.com 2012-12-10

# Design Observer

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) explains the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information by Observer Omnimedia LLC (“Observer”) on its Design Observer and related web channels: Observatory, Change Observer, Places and Observer Media (collectively, the “Design Observer Group Sites”). Observer appreciates your readership and the value of your personal privacy. We respect the personal nature of the information you may provide to us on the Design Observer Group Sites and acknowledge the importance of protecting this information.

Non-personally identifiable information such as site usage information is occasionally collected indirectly and automatically about your activities while visiting the Design Observer Group Sites, including what pages you view and when you view them and information about the browser you are using. Site usage information is used to help us understand how our sites are being used and for systems administration purposes and may be shared in aggregate form with third parties. We never link browsing information to the personal information you submit to us.

We collect personal information when you provide it to us by sending an email to us or signing up to receive a newsletter or posting comments.

We may disclose and use personal information in special circumstances when it is necessary to enforce our User Agreement or this Privacy Policy, or when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to disclose your personal information to third parties. This policy does not protect information you post to any on-line comment board, chat room, newsgroup, job board or other public forum within the Design Observer Group Sites.

The personal information we collect from you is stored on our data host’s secure servers. Within Observer, only authorized personnel have access to your information. Despite our best efforts, no transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, you provide us with your personal information at your own risk.

The Design Observer Group Sites contain many links to other sites on the Internet. Observer cannot control and is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other web sites.

Observer does not knowingly collect personal information from users under thirteen years of age. If we discover that a person under thirteen years of age has submitted his or her personal information to us, we will delete his or her personal information from our files. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under thirteen years of age who you believe has shared his or her personal information with us, please contact us at by email at designobserver [at] winterhouse.com or by mail at P.O. Box 159, Falls Village, CT 06031. If you are under thirteen years of age, please do not submit any personal information to us without first having your parent or guardian send us consent at one of the above addresses.

Observer’s Privacy Policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our Privacy Policy.
